JONATHAN LaPAGLIA:
Give me your torch.
The tribe has spoken.
(OVER RADIO) Flight 111,
you're clear for landing. Runway 3.
Roger.
Abort! Abort!
There's a person on the runway.
Of course I had to come out
of maternity leave for this.
What would a global showdown be
without me?
I have played the most days
of Australian Survivor
out of any person.
I have done my bit,
and I need to get paid.
I still don't have a Chanel bag,
and as always, I wouldn't mind
a little tan top-up.
JONATHAN: This season,
seven of Australia's best
are taking to the beaches of Samoa.
Surprise, mother trucker!
(LAUGHS)
The king of the jungle
is back, baby.
# Da-da-da! #
It's like I'm in the Olympics
for lying, cheating
and stealing.
(LAUGHS)
This is my third season,
and there is
a long list of things
that you haven't even
seen me do yet,
which is, like...
one of them would be win.
(LAUGHS)
Fighting for the title
is a devious mastermind...
..and a strategic rebel.
I am now a part of history,
playing against
the world's best.
But I'm the rebel queen.
The last time I played,
every move that I made
was a blindside.
So, this season,
I've got that taste in my mouth
and I want it back.
Joining them is
the godmother of negotiation.
People see me as
a hard-nosed bitch
businessperson
because I can wheel and deal
like the best of them.
And a mad king.
I've grown a lot as a person
since the last time
I played Survivor.
My arse has doubled in size.
I'm coming in hot
with this dad bod.
The motto I live by
is "glory or death".
Nobody has been a more powerful
player in Australian Survivor
than me.
Nobody.
I played basically
the perfect game of Survivor
and I won
half a million dollars.
That was the completion
of a dream.
If there was one thing
that was going to make me
play this game again,
it's to represent my country
and play on behalf of Australia.
We're not looking for
the goat "maaa-aa-aa".
We're looking for the GOAT -
the greatest of all time.
Golden God is back!
Uhhh!
This is a tribe
of extraordinary players.
(HORN HONKS)
SHONEE: Ahh! (LAUGHS)
Who is that?
Giants of the game.
Yo!
(ALL EXCLAIM AND CHEER)
(LAUGHS)
With a history rich in rivalry
and old bonds.
(BOTH LAUGH)
I thought, there's no way.
But now they have to face
their toughest opponents yet.
The World.
At the helm
of the invading force...
..the USA,
where it all began.
I would say
I'm a Survivor legend.
I played Survivor three times
and I won twice.
I won ¤3 million.
Right now, this season of
Survivor is going to be short
and fast,
and that's my gameplay.
I'm fast and I'm furious.
I hit the ground running,
and when it's on, it's on.
King of the jungle.
I'm building a spy shack.
Spy nest. And I'm
going to hear everything.
The winner of Survivor Cagayan,
Tony.
But this time around,
I'm not here for the money.
I'm here for the glory.
I want the world title
of Sole Survivor.
These are the originals.
Legends who broke the mould...
..and built a reputation
of cutthroat gameplay.
Oh, sweet little baby Aussies.
Think they know how to play
Survivor. They're so cute.
(LAUGHS)
I've been playing this game
for decades. For decades.
This will be my fifth time
playing Survivor.
Everyone all said that I'm
the most dangerous player
out here,
so...I guess they're right.
The winner of Survivor
Fans Vs Favourites.
So, I've won it once,
I should have won it twice,
and I'm here to win it again
on the world stage.
The last time
I was here in Samoa,
I had a bitter jury,
so I lost by a few votes.
So I am here to claim the win
that was meant to be mine
16 years ago.
They'll be joined by the best
the world has to offer.
A deadly triple threat.
I was in season 2
of Survivor Quebec, and...
(SPEAKS QUEBEC FRENCH)
A strategic assassin.
I'm the once and forever
reigning champion
of Survivor New Zealand.
(LAUGHS) Because it got
cancelled after I won.
And the Nordic wolf.
No-one knows this guy
from Finland.
You're gonna be surprised.
He got game.
I smile a lot, but, like,
this is my poker face.
And completing this tribe,
a charming puppet-master.
I played Survivor South Africa
once before, and I won.
My eyes. They have
the ability to hypnotise.
Gets very dangerous
the longer you're around me.
My sole objective
is to restore balance
to the world of Survivor.
You've got Australians
running around
calling themselves
gods and kings.
So I'm here to give them
a long-overdue
devil of a thrashing,
compliments of Africa.
(LAUGHS)
The Aussies must unite
and see past their differences
to defeat
these international
heavyweights.
It's a battle
25 years in the making.
Best of the best going head
to head for that ultimate title.
This is Australia
versus the World.
16 days, 14 people,
one survivor.
Come on in.
LUKE: Oooh.
Hello, hello.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
Well, hello.
Jonathan.
GEORGE: Long time, no see, JLP.
Long time, no see.
Welcome back.
Wow.
There you have it.
The seven of you represent
some of the best players
Australia has to offer.
And I think it's fair to say
your gameplay is up there
with the best in the world.
Indeed.
So I sent out a few invitations
to see what would happen
when the best of Australian
Survivor
goes up against
the best in the world.
Wow.
Come on in.
LUKE: Hey! Who we got here?
SARAH: Oh, my God. Here we go.
Oh, my...
Oh, my God, it's Cirie.
I heard my name. Great.
GEORGE: Oh, my God, those guns!
Rob Bentele
might be the biggest unit here.
Wow.
Bloody hell.
What, what, what!
Parv on the end.
Hi, Parv!
Hi!
Well, this is quite the line-up.
First of all, I want to thank
you for accepting our invitation
and coming out to play
Australian Survivor.
We really appreciate that.
The seven of you are some
of the greatest, most iconic
and devastatingly effective
players the world has ever seen,
and you've travelled a long way
to get here -
from the US, South Africa,
New Zealand, Quebec
and as far as Finland.
And personally, I'd like to
thank you for coming out here
to show these Aussies
just how it's done.
Thank you for inviting us.
Welcome to
Australia Versus The World.
(ALL CHEER)
This is so good.
So, Shonee.
Yes.
You've played a lot of Survivor.
Maybe not quite as much as
Parvati.
I mean, she has, you know,
more days than you in the game.
But you're right up there,
no doubt.
Thanks.
So what keeps bringing you back?
It's just like this love/hate
relationship with this game.
You think you're retired and
you're like, "Yep, I'm done,"
and then next minute
you're like, "Fine,
"I'll buy a little red tee dress
and I'll be back."
Can't keep me away.
So, Kirby,
there's four winners over there
and only one over here.
Actually, Tony's a two-time
winner, so technically,
it's five winners.
Thanks for that, Jonathan.
You bet.
I mean, isn't that just
a little bit intimidating?
Well, I'm the baby of the group -
I've only played once,
and I didn't watch it
before coming on,
so...I've kept that the same,
so I don't know any of youse,
which...I don't know, that
could be a detriment, maybe.
It could work in my advantage.
Well, Tony,
I'm kind of surprised.
I expected some trash talk
from the Aussies,
but there's nothing.
No, they're a lovely
bunch of people.
Um... However, I do think
that they did make a mistake.
The world title is at stake.
This ain't just
a regular Sole Survivor title.
This is the world title.
I think we're ready to lose
limbs out here for that.
So, Cirie, you're known as
the greatest Survivor player
that has never won.
Wah-wah.
Wah-wah. I know.
(OTHERS LAUGH)
Is this game
going to change that?
Well, that remains to be seen,
doesn't it, Jonathan?
I'm here, and I'm here
like Tony -
I'm here to lose a limb.
Alright, well, it's clear you've
all come out to play,
and play hard.
But make no mistake, this is
going to be a season
like no other.
It is going to be fast.
It is going to be furious.
And not only are you
from different countries,
but you're from different worlds
of Survivor.
But in the end,
it's going to come down to
those three little
magical words -
outwit, outplay, and outlast -
and whoever does it the best
is going to walk out of here
with a quarter million dollars,
but maybe more importantly,
with the title of the greatest
Survivor player of all time.
Wow.
Is it going to be an Aussie?
Is it going to be someone
from the World tribe?
We'll find out
in 16 very intense days.
Alright, enough of me talking.
You're gonna need these.
(SQUEALS)
Well done, Shon.
Well done, Shonee!
That IS a great start.
Go ahead. Put them on.
Oh, gimme that buff!
No, I...I missed the invite.
Cute!
CIRIE: And go, baby!
Alright. Are you ready to get
to your first reward challenge?
Yes!
Yes, sir!
For today's challenge...
..you're going to
race down a slide...
..scramble under a net,
and then throw sandbags
at a bell.
First person to ring the bell...
(DING!)
..will get to choose one item
from this shelf.
Want to know
what you're playing for?
Yeah.
Sure.
Everything you need...
Look at that!
Oh, my goodness gracious.
..to kick-start your game.
Tarp. Comfort items.
Basket of fruit. Tea and coffee.
Shonee, some champagne
to celebrate that first day.
Yeah, it's a celebration!
The all-important flint.
Boring.
(OTHERS LAUGH)
And whatever's in this box.
Oooh!
Ohh.
Oh. I think we need that.
Worth playing for?
ALL: Yes!
Alright, I'm going to give you
a minute to strategise,
and then we're gonna get it on.
Let's go!
Booyah!
What's in the box?!
Jeepers creepers.
Alright, Aussies,
who do you want to put up?
The Golden God.
For green and gold.
Come on, golden boy.
Might as well.
Are you gonna go?
Alright, come on, Rob, let's go.
(OTHERS SHOUT SUPPORT)
GEORGE: Go get him.
Let's go!
South Africa!
DAVID: Hey, I got
a proposition for you.
Yeah?
I want you in the end game.
I think, like, uh, I go, you go.
So I need you deep, dude.
They're going to be
coming for us super early.
So here's my proposition.
Yeah?
I will give you input
into who goes home
on the Australian tribe
if you do the same thing for me.
You played one of the greatest
games I've ever seen, brother.
OK?
Think on it. You can tell me
after. Give me the signal.
Alright, here we go.
First round.
We have the Golden God
from Australia
taking on Zulu Rob
from the World.
That's a lot of beef up there.
(LAUGHS) Grade A.
For reward, Survivors ready?
Go!
(ONLOOKERS CHEER
AND SHOUT SUPPORT)
Rob gets the jump.
GEORGE: Wow, what a transition!
SHONEE: It was like a fish!
David trying to catch him.
They both get to the sandbags.
(DING!)
Rob takes it out. Hits the bell.
That's some Zulu stuff right
there.
I'm glad you're here.
First one for World.
(CHEERING, LAUGHING)
Alright, Rob,
what do you want to choose?
LUKE: Oh, he's gone for the box.
Oh, yes! Mystery box.
Alright. It's a mystery.
Nice.
CIRIE: No, as long as we keep it
out of their hands, it's good.
Ooh, interesting.
What'll we do with it?
Alright, here we go. Next round.
JANINE: Come on, budgie
smugglers!
We have Tommi for World
taking on George for Australia.
Are you good at sports?
No. Terrible.
Survivors ready?
Go!
SHONEE: Oh, my God!
George gets the jump!
Oh!
(ONLOOKERS EXCLAIM)
Holy moly!
Tommi takes
a hard hit on the neck.
He dusts himself off,
gets to the bags first.
Struggling to connect.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Yah!
(DING!)
Yeah!
That's it!
George does it for Australia.
Georgie boy!
Yes, baby!
Whoo!
George is a beast, man.
I think I
am going to take the flint
and make our life
a little bit easier.
Yeah. There you go.
SARAH: Well done, Georgie.
One-nil for challenges.
Who would have thought?
Alright. Australia,
who are you putting up?
Alright. Kirby.
World?
PARVATI: Should I go?
OK. I'll go.
Parvati.
I ain't scared of Kirby.
(LAUGHS)
Come on up.
The baby.
Yeah.
Alright. Survivors ready?
Go!
GEORGE: Go, Kirby!
Neck and neck down the slides.
TONY: Go, go, go, go!
CIRIE: Go!
Nice, nice.
You there, you there!
You got it, you got it.
Parvati with a slight lead.
Is this going to help her?
Oh! (BLEEP)
Kirby gets there last.
(DING!)
But she takes it out!
(CHEERING)
Yeah, Kirby!
Takes the fruit basket.
They could be hungry after that.
Alright.
We have Tony for World...
We got to try to look like
these guys, man.
Yeah. So anyways...
(BABBLES NONSENSE, LAUGHS)
..taking on Luke for Australia.
Go!
(ONLOOKERS SHOUT SUPPORT)
Luke gets the jump.
Off the slide first.
DAVID: Go get it, get it,
get it, get it.
Come on, Tony!
(DING!)
And that is it!
(AUSSIES CHEERING)
We'll take the tarp.
We're gonna be dry! Yeah!
Whoo!
Alright. Survivors ready? Go!
GEORGE: Go, Sarah!
PARVATI: Let's go, Cirie!
We have Sarah for Australia
taking on Cirie for World.
(DING!)
(ALL CHEER)
Alright.
This is what we're taking.
Cirie taking the comfort item.
GEORGE: Yeah. Nothing like
a woollen blanket in Samoa.
We are watching you.
(LAUGHS)
Survivors ready? Go!
(ONLOOKERS SHOUT SUPPORT)
Kass for World
taking on Janine for Australia.
GEORGE: Look at that transition.
Go, Janine!
(DING!)
(WORLD CHEERS)
Kass does it!
Oh, I'd love a tea!
Going to go with
the coffee and tea.
Yeah!
Here we go. Final round.
Lisa for World
taking on Shonee for Australia.
OK, I'm ready.
Shonee, the most important
reward is still left
on the shelf.
Come on, Lisa!
Do it for the bubbly.
How much do you like champagne?
So much. What about y...
I know you do.
I love it.
Survivors ready?
JANINE: Come on, Shon! (CLAPS)
You got this.
Go!
(ONLOOKERS SHOUT SUPPORT)
Lisa gets the jump.
(SQUEALS)
TONY: There you go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Shonee desperately trying
to close it down.
Quick under the net.
She gets to the bags first.
Can she close this out?
Oh!
She misses.
Lisa going for the win.
(DING!)
(ALL CHEER)
And Lisa does it for World!
ROB: Was that one throw?
Insane. That was one throw?
That is it.
TONY: That's all you need.
Good effort, Shon.
So unlucky when you can't throw.
Well done.
(LAUGHS)
Good job! (LAUGHS)
One throw?! Are you kidding me?
Alright, everyone.
Head out to your new camps,
and good luck.
GEORGE: Let's go!
Let's get this game started.
TONY: We only have 16 days.
This is going to be
fast and furious.
This is gonna be scrambling,
building alliances,
talking about
who's gonna go home.
I don't think the fans know
what this is gonna be about,
how fast this is gonna move.
Their heads
are gonna be spinning.
TONY: Home sweet home.
CIRIE: Oh, my God,
it's beautiful.
ROB: Whoo!
Wow.
Australia versus the World
is going to be the showdown
of the century.
Buckle up, kids.
This is a 16-day game with
the best from around the world.
This is, like, juiced-up
Survivor to the extreme.
Home sweet home.
Oh, so we can't
even open the box?
Maybe there's a key in...
This key could be anywhere.
And we've won two bottles
of champagne.
To me, there's
an obvious place to start.
Well done, guys.
(OTHERS CHEER)
In a game that's
as fast as this one,
relationships are gonna
have to solidify really fast.
The World!
ALL: Cheers!
What do you say?
Kippis?
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
Kippis!
Cheers.
Cheers!
So, do we want to just
officially introduce ourselves
and where we're from?
Yeah, of course.
Oh, OK, then I'll start.
I'm Cirie.
Obviously, I'm from
the United States.
OK? (LAUGHS) Next?
OK.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for sharing.
My name is Tony.
I'm from the USA.
There does seem to be
seven individuals
meeting each other out here.
So, I'm Rob.
I'm from South Africa.
It's my second time
playing Survivor.
But there's four internationals
and three Americans out here.
My name is Lisa
and I live in New Zealand.
My name is Kass
and I played Survivor Quebec.
Tommi. Played two years ago.
I lost by one vote.
(OTHERS EXCLAIM)
Yeah.
We have to stay US strong
until merge.
Alright.
So, bamboo, palm fronds.
OK, off we go.
Oh, look at you
taking the big ones, eh?
I've been lifting weights,
you know?
(CHUCKLES)
To prepare. I gotta get my muscles
big as yours so I can compete.
But the thing is,
Tony's a loose cannon.
I don't know about Tony.
Is he gonna trust me? Is he gonna
want to work with me?
I need to talk to you
about you and me.
OK.
Because I feel like...
I'm a little bit nervous.
You shouldn't be.
What I'm nervous about is...
(QUIETER) What I'm nervous about
is three of us.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm nervous about.
But it could be good.
Well, perception.
If we pull in...
Percep... Perception.
Yeah.
But I've got Cirie out here.
It's been over 15 years
since we've played together,
but that's my girl.
I love Cirie.
She talks out of the side of her
mouth when she's strategising.
(LAUGHS) It's the best.
I think you, me and Tony should
try to keep each other safe
till merge.
I agree.
OK. I'm not gonna hang out
with you very much.
Yeah. Me either. Alright.
Parvati and I go WAY back,
to Micronesia. (LAUGHS)
We had an all-girls alliance
called the Black Widow Brigade,
and it worked flawlessly.
We're spinning the guys around
as much as we can
till they don't know
which way is up,
and then we're devouring them
one at a time.
Nat, tell them that if he
were to give you the necklace,
that would redeem him
and we would vote for Amanda.
Who would fall for that?
I want to give individual
immunity to Natalie.
You officially go down as
the dumbest Survivor ever.
And then Parv went on
to win that season.
MY season.
That I SHOULD have won.
(LAUGHS)
Now, us, the Americans,
we walked in
with a huge target on our back,
so I can see
maybe something happening
with the other World tribe
members
that are not from the US.
And you can't help but notice
Rob off having conversations.
The Americans, yeah.
Yes.
Really?
Listen, guys, if the Americans
take one of us out,
they will dominate this tribe.
Yeah.
LISA: I've been a fan of Survivor
since the very first episode.
I love it so much.
When there was
a New Zealand version,
I just thought,
"I can never go on Survivor."
Like, "What?" Like, "Me?"
And I did it. (LAUGHS) I did it.
I won the very first time
I played Survivor.
So few people get to live out
their dream in life once,
and I'm getting to do it twice.
Me?
Yeah. (LAUGHS)
Yeah.
I think we all are. Yeah, yeah.
Like, talk about lifelong dreams
coming true.
Being able to meet
frickin' Cirie Fields.
If you're watching this now
and you don't understand,
like, go and watch
some more Survivor.
Go and watch
all of Cirie's seasons
and come back to me and say,
"Oh, I'm really sorry, Lisa.
You were right."
Yeah.
Um...
Uh-huh?
But...
..like everyone in the world,
you're my favourite Survivor
player, right?
Aw! Thank you.
I'll never go against you.
I know. But listen...
Do you know, this is going to be
fast and furious,
and I know New Zealanders
are laid back.
I don't have any allegiance
to anybody here.
I will never turn against you.
Look at me in the eyes
so you know.
But I have no desire
to ever turn against you.
I would love to play this game
with you.
Especially if we can
make it to the merge
and kind of get
with the Australians
and see what happens.
The non-US players -
Rob, Kass, Tommi and I -
are really trying
to build a nice alliance,
a very sensible alliance,
but now maybe Cirie and I
have something too.
Ridiculous that I can say
Cirie and I have something.
Just ridiculous!
There's huge targets here,
and we're not one of them. So...
If I had to, like, choose...
Don't know what to do.
This is the worst position
anyone playing Survivor
has ever been put at.
LUKE: Alright, alright.
Mad, huh?
GEORGE: Wow!
SARAH: How cool's this?
It's beautiful.
JANINE: Oh, my God.
Heya!
Oh, here's our stuff.
Home sweet home.
(CHUCKLES)
Here we are.
(OTHERS EXCLAIM)
Amazing.
Here I am, looking around at
the rest of this Aussie tribe.
They are the best of the best.
Am I legitimately worried?
Yes, I am.
I've got a big problem here.
So, who has played together
before?
What are... what are the combos
we're working with?
Aren't you a superfan, Sarah?
I know, I know. I just want
to... I want it out in the open.
I don't have
the pre-existing relationships
that people like David and Luke
have on this tribe.
(BOTH LAUGH)
The only relationship that I
have on this tribe is Shonee.
But she's got an axe to grind
against me
because I voted her out
the last time we were both here
on this island.
So the first thing I need to do
is clear the air with Shonee.
Because if I reunite
the Spice Girls,
we'll be able to work together.
And Shonee and George
is a very dangerous and fun
combination in this game.
Yeah, I've been good. Yeah,
just chilling. What about you?
Well, here's what I would
like to tell you, Shon.
Mm-hm?
I have absolutely no animosity
towards you...
..and I hope the feeling is
mutual!
(LAUGHS)
Yeah.
I swear to God, Shon,
I'm looking around and going,
"The only person
that I've played with
"and have a connection with..."
is you.
When it's good,
it's really good.
And do you know
what I tell myself?
And when it's bad,
it's really bad.
When it's bad, it's bad, but it
took 34 days to get bad
last time.
We're only here for 16.
This is only 16.
So I'm just like... It looks
like it's going to be peaking
right then
and it's going to be
in the good spot. (CHUCKLES)
So you would legitimately
want to work with me?
I would think that's
a very exciting alliance.
Mmm.
I definitely would.
It does make sense.
It makes sense because...
..we'd kind of protect each other
until merge.
I don't want to work with George
under any circumstances.
I really appreciate it, Shon.
I really do.
Yeah, it's good.
Red flag number one -
George has written a book
about manipulation.
I have been a victim of that.
But I do not have pre-existing
relationships on this tribe
other than George.
Getting nowhere.
Do you know what?
None of youse care.
Ooh!
Coming into this game,
I need to lower my threat level.
And that's why
I'm not going to have
any sort of public
ride-or-die relationships.
Things need to be kept in
secret.
How are you feeling?
Yeah, I was gonna ask you
the same.
How are you? Where are you at?
Well...
OK.
Yeah.
(LAUGHS) Why?
Well, I think that, like,
obviously, you and I
have a clean slate.
There's no bad blood straight
out of the gate,
you know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just feel like
it could be good.
Do we make us a secret,
solid alliance?
Yes.
And that way,
we can just sort of
keep an eye out.
Mmm. Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm...
I'm not in Samoa for the great
weather or the fine dining.
I am here
because I want revenge.
And I have one name on my list
now, and that's George.
Dad bod is in.
Mm-hm.
This is my victory tour.
It's going to be iconic.
I-Shon-ic. (LAUGHS)
GEORGE: I feel happy.
I'm happy I'm back.
Me too.
Do you know what I'm thinking?
The water. Do you want to go.
Who's keen for a dip?
An ocean dip.
I've still got some...
(LAUGHTER)
Sorry, guys. There's only
so many hours in the day.
You know.
I really feel like I was
born to play this game.
Being back here,
it just feels, like, natural.
This game is in my DNA.
I've already
played with half of these guys.
How are you doing?
Yeah. Good.
We're good, I'm good.
Yeah. 100%.
But I'm the only winner
on the Australian tribe,
so I feel like
I'm pretty exposed out here.
So for me, the only
thing to do is play bigger.
So immediately off the bat,
I'm looking in the fruit basket
searching for idols.
I spoke to South African Rob
openly at the challenge today.
It's like the Olympics
of Survivor, right?
Lucky I'm Usain Bolt.
You don't want to be the Raygun
of the Australian Olympic team.
That's kind of George.
OK. Open it.
Oh, wow. This is huge.
Dude, this is...
How big this is.
Huge.
Are you trying
to steal my best friend?
What's going on here?
I'm George from Bankstown.
Lovely to finally meet you.
Yeah. I'm good, I'm good.
I know George might be
the strategy genius,
but he's someone
that has always felt like
he has to live up
to my shadow strategically.
Not everyone wants
to live up to perfection.
It's tricky,
but he's also
a huge target.
That's very useful
for someone like me,
who is clearly the number one
target in this game.
How are you doing?
I'm doing good.
What are we doing?
Yeah, let's just get into it.
Honestly, I'd love to work with
you and Luke
and be the buffer that protects us
and propels us forward.
But we're all shields
to each other.
That's why I call it
the buffer strategy.
So, I'll be I'll be super honest
and open with you right now.
I'm not voting you
off no matter what.
I just can't.
I worry about you after merge,
because after merge,
I'm in big trouble.
He's in really big trouble.
You shouldn't.
You've got some people
that just don't have
the same reputation in the game
that the king of the jungle,
the Golden God
and the King of Bankstown have.
You know?
(LAUGHTER)
Would this not be
the best alliance ever?
Like, seriously, one of the most
exciting alliances ever.
It would be good.
Ever.
It would be pretty good.
It'll break the internet.
Yeah.
Oh...
What are we calling ourselves?
If you want to call our alliance
the Power Bottoms,
I'm all for it, David.
(LAUGHTER)
I'm just humouring George.
Yeah, the boys are on the bottom,
so we're the power bottom.
Alright.
He might be
a bit of a strategic master,
but he has got
zero self-awareness
in comparing his game to mine.
Like, George,
you have never won, dude.
And you're trying to tell me
you can be a shield for me.
OK, bubby. OK.
Yeah.
(LAUGHTER)
I bet you we'll get this fire
before they do with the flint.
I bet you.
Cheers.
Yeah.
Rob is a fire guy.
Go. Go as fast as you can.
OK. Yeah.
Like that.
Like that?
We should have something now, man.
Alright, look,
I'm giving up here.
I've played Survivor
five times now,
and I know this game is less
about surviving the elements,
and it's more
about surviving each other.
How close are Aussies
and New Zealand in general?
Oh, it's a bit of a like...
Like Finland and Sweden.
You tell me. Maybe.
There are four players from
the world
and three players
from the United States.
So I don't
want to make it too obvious
that I'm working with Cirie
to bring in some other people.
Your shirt is gonna be like...
Yeah.
It's, like, the most dangerous
thing you could touch.
OK, I'm gonna stick with you.
I feel like
you've got the survivalism.
My plan is to go
head over to South Africa
and talk to the Zulu king.
I tend to eat guys like Rob
for breakfast,
but Rob gives me options.
So, I want to get him on my side
as quickly as I possibly can.
I need Rob magnetised to me.
These are the ones.
The only people I know
are Cirie and Tony.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
How are things? I don't know.
Fine, I guess.
Yours are beautiful. Stop!
You're doing that to me.
The web weaving has begun.
And I'm, like, three steps ahead.
I saw Rob and David
clicking at the challenge.
I know David from another show,
so I'm thinking
I can use this David connection
to build a bridge with Rob maybe.
I haven't seen South African
Survivor, but I know who you are.
How?
Because David loves you.
David?
David on the other side.
How do you know that?
Because David and I
played a game together.
Big secret.
You guys just got off
another show?
Yeah. Cannot tell anyone this.
Yeah. Of course.
OK. It's called
Deal or No Deal Island.
He loves you.
He wants to play with you.
I can see.
You can tell.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
I would like to play with him
too.
So, I think the stronger, bigger
threats going into merge
is probably an important thing
to keep together.
Yeah.
But keep that between us, please.
I promise.
That's how you can trust me.
Yes, exactly.
That's actually a perfect way.
You just gave me something
I can prove to you.
I am working with Rob
and working Rob simultaneously.
I'm still the Black Widow.
And I'll still wrap you up
in my web and suck your blood.
Yeah, that's what I'm hoping.
ROB: Part of Parvati's gameplay
is to be flirtatious.
But Parvati, nah. Sorry, boss.
Not gonna work here.
We've got a solid four -
Tommi, Kass, Lisa and myself.
Literally all you need
in this game.
We're the only people
who are alone here.
You've got seven horses
for Australia.
Yeah.
You've got three horses
for America.
Our countries
have one horse in this race.
One of us leaves
the Americans tear us to pieces.
I can promise you one thing.
An American will go home first
from the World tribe.
That is a promise that I promise you
I will not break.
Sorry. Not sorry.
Day Two. And it's my birthday.
I don't think I've ever celebrated
a birthday on Survivor.
This is a first for me.
Out of five seasons.
Oh.
Thanks, guys.
She said all she wants for her
birthday is an immunity win.
One immunity. Can we deliver?
Yeah. We can.
If I stay in this game tonight,
I am tied
for the most amount of days
played for Survivor ever.
152, with my boy Boston Rob.
And I'm coming for that record.
Yeah. This is not
the Australian side.
They would do it just
because it is your birthday.
Come on in.
Hello.
So, Cirie.
How were your first 24 hours
on the beach?
Fabulous. Wonderful.
We enjoyed
getting to know each other
over a couple glasses
of champagne.
Relax. Chill.
Parvati,
you've played a lot of Survivor.
Does this feel like business as usual
or is this a whole other ball game?
I think
the more Survivor you play,
the less you care about surviving.
(LAUGHTER)
Did you get fire?
We had so much fire.
It was so hot.
Alright. OK. So, George,
do you think they've managed
to open that mystery box?
Who knows what's in the box?
Tell us.
Yeah, tell us what's in the box.
Alright. Shall we get to it?
ALL: Oh, yeah.
Alright. For today's challenge,
you're going to work together
to move a heavy staircase
and use it to climb over a wall.
You'll then use giant blocks
to build another staircase
to reach the top of the tower.
Finally, two of you
will use a slingshot
to fire coconuts
at a series of targets.
The first tribe to smash
all their targets wins immunity.
And this...
..is the immunity idol.
This is what you want. With this
back at camp, you are safe.
Guaranteed another day
in the game.
Without it, you're going to be
seeing me at Tribal Council,
where one of you will become
the first person voted out of
Australia Versus the World.
No-one wants to be that person.
GEORGE: No.
Alright, I'll give you
a minute to strategise.
Let's get to it.
Alright, here we go for immunity.
Survivors, ready?
Go!
Go! Go that way.
That staircase is a beast.
Three, two, one.
Come on, guys.
Push it, push it! Go, go!
Wow! World tribe
quick out of the gate!
Nice.
Almost there, almost there,
almost there.
They're at the wall.
Now everyone's got to go
over the top.
Come on, Aussies,
you're falling behind. Let's go.
Come on! Let's go, Aussie!
Go!
There you are.
Now you're at the wall.
Go! Go!
World tribe almost over.
Aussies trying to close the gap.
Tony last to go over
for World tribe.
Thanks.
Looks good. Go, World.
Now you've got six giant blocks.
You need to wrestle them into
position and build another staircase.
OK. Now slack.
Not working, not working.
Keep flipping it.
Flip it. Flip it.
It's fine.
Go, DJ.
Go, Aussies!
David's over. You're good.
Go, Australia! Let's go.
Someone be the brains!
Get this up the right way.
Is this the right side?
No, no! Stop! Stop, stop!
It's gonna spin twice.
Closer?
Not only do you have to have
your blocks in position,
but they need to be
the correct orientation.
Fingers clear.
The symbols need to be
the right way up.
OK. Again, again.
Aussies have their first block
in position.
Working on their seconds.
Let's go. Shon, we're gonna do this
box this time. Go.
Go back. Go back, go back!
World have their first block
in position.
That way?
Come this way.
No, it's on the floor.
Yeah. No, but let's just straighten
it out. Let's just do a flip.
Aussies slowing down.
Meanwhile, World tribe,
a well-oiled machine.
Here we go.
Lower, lower, lower.
We're almost there.
Lower, lower.
Perfect.
World now have three in position.
First row is the easy one.
Now it gets tricky.
Now.
One more.
It's gonna spin twice
when you get to there. Closer.
Now you've got to get those giant
blocks on top of that first row.
The mouth facing to the floor.
There's two rows up. Alright?
Push, push, push.
That's it.
Tony, Rob, Tommi.
Getting that first one up.
Is it right?
You just need
to slide it back into position.
That's it.
Three. Two. One. Go, go!
Aussies working on their second row.
Gonna try the side approach.
Stop.
David, Luke, George and Sarah
wrestle that next one up.
No, no, no, it's the wrong side.
Yeah, but we can rotate it
from up there.
Drop the box.
World have five blocks in position.
That final block
is the most difficult.
Come on, guys.
It's going to take a lot of effort
to get it all the way to the top.
This box has to get up first.
Trust me.
Leave it. It's fine.
It's fine.
It has to get to the top.
No. This one.
No. This one to the top.
Once we have this,
we can't get to that.
Yes, that's what
I'm trying to say.
World tribe's arguing. That opens
the window for the Aussie tribe.
Good teamwork.
Watch fingers.
Teamwork, teamwork, teamwork.
Slide, slide, slide!
Alright, baby, here we go.
Same again.
Now we're back even.
Push.
We are back.
Hold on, Dave.
Aussies down to their last block.
We need to get this up.
Hurry!
Three. Two. One. Go!
Both tribes
taking a different approach.
Yeah. Stay under it.
Stay under it.
We're there.
Pick it up.
Whoa!
What's up?
Almost losing it.
It's about to topple over.
Here we go. Give me a gap.
I gotta get under.
Yes, David. Get under, David.
It's David going up,
using his back.
Whoa!
He's doing it all by himself.
That is crazy.
(DAVID GRUNTS)
Three, two, one, push.
Deadlift.
What a beast the Golden God is!
What an effort!
Aussies almost have it done.
(WORLD TRIBE ARGUES)
Down. Down.
Take this one!
They did the same thing. Look.
And that is it.
David and Luke get that final block
into position.
Go, go!
They're moving on.
It's David on the slingshot first.
Winds up.
Goes long.
Australia has a huge lead.
It's going to give them plenty of
time to work out that slingshot.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Rob underneath that final block.
Taking the cue from Australia.
Keep going.
There it is. They get it up.
Good job.
Alright. Who's going up?
Come on, Luke.
Takes out the first target
for Australia.
Come on, let's go.
There it is. You're good, World.
Let's go, let's go.
It's Rob and Tony.
Keep passing them to me.
Going up for World.
I need to...
Come on, guys,
you can even it up.
Slow down.
(CHEERING)
Australia gets another one.
World still trying
to figure it out.
Desperate to close that gap.
Tony in now. He winds up.
Tony does it.
Do that again.
He connects again.
Oh, shit.
We are tied - two each.
Yeah.
David connects.
(PANEL SHATTERS)
Oh, my word!
And Luke connects.
World does it again.
Take your time, mate.
Yeah.
And again for Australia.
And another one.
Australia down to
their final two targets.
You can do it.
Tony does it.
(CHEERING)
Yes! One more!
Australia hit another target.
They're down
to their final target.
Come on. Come on.
David winding it up.
Going for the win.
(CHEERS)
David wins immunity for Australia.
Bad luck, boys. Hey, bad luck.
Yeah.
It must be on your side.
It's quite serious
whatever's in there.
We'll find it. We'll find it.
Remember what we said, eh?
Yeah, yeah. No, it's the start.
It's the start.
He's asking for the key.
Australia, Congratulations.
Immunity is yours.
(CHEERING)
Aussies!
Let's go.
Alright. You are safe.
Nobody going home.
Head back to camp.
Enjoy your night off.
Lead the way, Golden God.
Alright.
Look at this, you guys.
Pretty cool.
Good luck, guys.
Thanks. Bye.
Goodbye.
Bye, guys.
Alright, World,
Tribal Council tonight,
where one of you will become
the first person voted out.
Grab your gear. Head back
to camp. I'll see you tonight.
Losing the first
immunity challenge is terrible,
but we've got a solid four -
Tommi, Kass, Lisa and myself
against three Americans.
This is a very simple vote.
They call Cirie the greatest
player that's never won.
And sorry not sorry.
That's not changing today, boss.
(LAUGHS)
Worst case scenario.
Damn, man.
That was just brute strength.
Yeah.
So, between
the four single countries,
Tommi, Lisa, Kass and myself.
This was discussed yesterday.
We stick together,
we take out an American.
It's a very simple, easy vote.
I'm with the four, Parvati's
there and I decide, hey,
let me bring her in on this,
into the inner circle
of this alliance.
So you want to talk game?
Who's going home tonight?
Where? What?
Who are we taking out tonight?
Yeah, you tell me.
You have the numbers.
You tell me.
What do you think?
You guys have four right here.
You're looking at me,
trying to ask me to tell you.
Ha-ha, we just lost one now.
(LAUGHTER)
Are you OK?
Nice try, buddy.
OK, so what do you say?
What do you think we do?
What do you say?
I'm waiting
to hear your suggestion.
How does Cirie sound?
What?
Cirie?
Yeah.
I mean, I love Cirie, but...
I know we do as well.
You guys are trying
to get a forum.
Trying to keep the tribe strong,
that's all.
We're not being unfair
or unreasonable.
And I think that's a very simplistic
way of looking at this,
the tribe dynamics.
This is a game of lots of different
people and personalities.
So, there's
a lot of things to consider.
So, I'll ask again. Then who?
Then who?
Then I need to think about it.
I think everyone needs to have
conversations with each other.
We have an afternoon to talk about
it and figure it out.
I try to give Parvati a beautiful
ticket out of this nonsense,
and she just rejected it
to my face.
So she has to go home.
The set-up is perfect.
We've got four players.
Let me go to Tony and Cirie
and bring them in on it.
If I get this right, that means
I am able to unify this tribe.
And that's what I need.
I need soldiers
to fight the oncoming battle.
What are your thoughts? Uh, Rob?
I came to find out
from you guys.
Where are your heads at?
I haven't scrambled with nobody.
I'm asking Cirie,
is anybody talking game to her?
Nobody's talking game to her
either.
Has anybody talked game to you?
Yeah.
People are trying to figure out
what to do.
OK. What are people
saying to you?
Are they saying, let's break
up the threat, get rid of Tony?
Or are they saying
stuff like that?
No.
OK.
OK. That's... I can tell you
straightaway.
OK.
No-one has said Tony.
Yeah, yeah.
It's being swung around a bit.
Um, I think you should... You should
go and chat to people.
People's biggest fear
is too many Americans.
Listen, if the group...
You're telling me my name
is on the chopping block?
Yes.
I'm going with the numbers, man.
Exactly.
Of course, Rob believes that I'm
doing exactly as I'm told.
Why wouldn't I listen to the king?
But listen, me and Parv rode before,
and this is not our first rodeo.
I've talked to you earlier.
That doesn't count.
Why doesn't it count?
That wasn't a real talk.
Then let's go talk.
Yeah.
OK.
I have been investing time
and energy into Rob.
I wanted this to work
between us.
Is this your game?
What?
You just try to bulldoze people into
doing what you want them to do.
I literally brought you in
with the four people
and I said, "Hey, join us."
I literally gave you, like,
everything you ever wanted
because I trusted you so much.
It's been so good since day one.
We've been great.
But now I feel like I'm completely
missing the mark with you,
because I feel like
you maybe have a big group of people
that you want to work with.
I don't see us as a group.
I see us as a you and me.
What name do you have in mind?
I can't say a name because
you're working with all of them.
She's one of the people
that I trust here.
I don't trust a lot of people
here. I trust her.
Who do you want to vote for?
I don't know,
vote for somebody else.
Whoever. Who do you want me
to vote for besides her?
It was a long-term plan to try
to keep the tribe strong thing.
Tell me.
Doesn't matter now anyway.
It doesn't matter now
because you're voting for me.
No, I didn't say that.
I mean, I'm, like,
I'm so offended.
I know that he's trying
to blindside me tonight.
Sir, you do not know
who you're messing with.
You don't, like, you don't blindside
the queen. You don't.
Where is everybody?
I have no idea. I'm just...
People are scrambling.
It's... It's unbelievable.
You're relaxed, you're calm.
Relaxed.
Rob thinks he's running this tribe.
So don't you usually
cut the head of the snake off?
Because we can't
have Rob telling Tommi,
Lisa, Kass, potentially Tony
what to do.
So Rob has to go.
So Rob suggested I talk to everybody
since my name
is being floated around.
By him.
Exactly.
I know,
but he's trying to make me think
that all of you are saying my name.
Huh?
Rob's plan is to vote out Parvati,
and he just wants me, Kass and
Tommi to just go along with it
because it's best
for us to just stay as a group.
But I don't
know how anyone thinks it's OK
to just dictate to people, like,
I don't know if you know this,
but I already won Survivor,
so I think I might know
what to do a little bit.
I'm so glad
Rob's working it out for us.
I wouldn't know what to do
if he wasn't.
My question though,
is who would vote Rob?
I would definitely vote Rob.
I know you would definitely
vote Rob.
Rob yesterday.
He's so good at everything.
Like starting a fire,
using a slingshot,
keeping track of a machete.
Do you see it?
(LAUGHTER)
Wait, I'm sorry I had to laugh,
like, you...
He sold a lot of tickets
that he has not delivered
on any of them yet.
For a first vote, Rob.
Very sensible.
But, um,
this is probably so stupid,
but I want to play with Cirie.
I want to play with Cirie.
Just us together. I just want that
to happen so bad.
If Parvati goes home tonight, it is
good for my relationship with Cirie.
Yeah.
After that...
Ladies.
I'm starting to get so stressed.
Every time I walk up to the
shelter, everyone stops talking.
I feel like I'm getting
blindsided.
Is it me?
I don't know.
Oh, my God. It's me.
Rob threw my name.
But...
Well, that's what I heard.
He thinks he's in charge.
And it's a little bit hard to...
What do we want to do?
I'll go with you girls, like, 100%.
OK. The rest of the girls
I think are OK with that.
We have to.
I'm doing it.
No! Stop! Stop, stop!
It's Rob. Rob. It's Rob!
It's Rob. Rob!
Say no more. I'm OK.
Alright.
My goodness.
I need to take a swim.
LISA: At the moment, I'm in
a pretty powerful position.
This is like, full-on Survivor.
So...
Yes.
I don't want to...
Yeah. I don't want to sound like
Rob, but Parvati or Rob.
Yeah.
They are both equal threat.
What do you think?
I'm just trying to think.
Pulling off this blindside means
the Black Widow is back.
I'm aligned with Tony and Cirie,
with Lisa, and with Kass.
So I think
we're going to vote Rob.
If I'm not being played,
which I could totally
be being played right now,
I'm aware of that.
This is Survivor.
So it's completely possible
that I'm aligned with nobody.
Alright, you know the drill.
Go ahead.
Grab a torch, come forward,
dip it in and get fire.
It's part of
the ritual of Tribal Council.
Because in this game,
fire represents your life.
Once it's gone, so are you.
Alright.
Parvati,
you've played more Survivor
than almost anyone else
in the world.
How does this game differ from
the other ones you've played?
Um, there's a lot
of differences here.
I think we're all kind of
adjusting
to how do we relate to each
other from different countries?
I've never had that experience
on Survivor before
and this game is pretty fast.
We're on day two.
We're looking at, like,
there's people crossing lines
at challenges,
trying to talk to the other side.
Rob, is that true?
Are people crossing lines
already with the other tribe?
Yes. Conversations are happening.
In Survivor,
you always have to listen,
especially to your enemy.
It's the Australians
versus the World.
If we hit merge and there's more
Australians than us,
we are all doomed.
Cirie.
How would you characterise
the pace of this game so far?
Um...
I would say top speed.
The game started
the second we hit the mats.
The game started the second you saw
people having conversations
and they weren't having those
conversations with you.
And typically, if conversations are
being had and you're not included,
you're probably in trouble.
Has that been the case for you?
Um...
Well, I think maybe it shifted
a little bit.
Initially, there wasn't
a lot of conversations,
but I feel a little bit better now
with conversations that I've had.
So, Tony, an obvious division
in this tribe
is three US players
against four players
who are not from the US.
Do you think that's going
to factor into tonight?
I hope not, Jonathan. I mean,
we're all here as tribe mates.
We're not from South Africa,
we're not from America.
We're just tribe mates that got
challenged by the Aussies.
And that's all that's on my mind.
But, Rob,
surely that's a valid strategy
for the four non-Americans
to stick together.
Possibly.
But the problem there is that you
then alienate people going forward.
So I believe it's not the time
to blindside anyone in this tribe
right now.
And I'm hoping and praying
that we can prove something that's
been very seldom done on Survivor,
where we can do a vote
that is 100% unified.
Yeah, Kass, it can't be 100% unified
because someone's going home tonight.
Yeah. Of course.
Um, but it can be close.
Parvati, are you concerned
that these non-Americans
are conspiring to take out
one of the Americans?
Yes. Very much.
That's been shared with me.
It's a clear way to divide the tribe
if we have to go to a vote.
Majority rules.
And if you're in the majority,
you have the power.
Cirie, usually at this stage
of any game of Survivor,
the conversation
turns to tribe strength.
Did that happen this afternoon?
Um, yeah, that was mentioned.
It was mentioned, but I kind
of think tribe strength
presents itself in many shapes
and colours, right?
So, if you're saying
tribe physical strength,
um, that's one aspect
of the game.
But the game is not
just physicality.
I definitely, I do agree, um,
with that,
physical strength is not the only
most important thing in this game.
And it's also looking at who you can
work with going forward
when we do start intertwining
with the other tribe,
because if one person cracks,
then they get through
and they annihilate us all.
So that kind of strength,
that mental fortitude,
that strength
to actually hold our line,
that is actually truly
the most important thing.
And that is basically
boiled down to loyalty.
Tonight is the first of many tests,
and each time we pass the test,
the loyalty and trust
get stronger.
So that means you want to keep
coming back to Tribal Council
to keep making tests?
No, no. Hopefully this is the last
time we come back like this.
Next time we come back,
there'll be Aussies amongst us
that we can take out.
Together.
Then how do you test that?
Well, I know that.
Because there's something
you didn't tell the tribe.
What?
I know about you and David.
She was going to turn on us first.
The second she got to David,
she was going to turn on us.
She leaked it yesterday.
That is not what happened.
I told Rob that David and I
played a game called Deal
or No Deal Island together.
And David loves Rob.
She made it clear that they played
well together in that game
and they went very far together.
That tells me that they have
a good relationship,
and I'm very petrified of
the day they get together again.
This is very interesting.
This is very interesting coming
from you at this moment
after we've seen you
communicating with David
multiple times in the challenges.
He comes to me.
And it's been very clear that
you want to work with David.
I know David from that game
that I played.
We played together
until he threw me under the bus.
Now we know what happened.
That's the deal.
I'm not watching no more.
Deal or No Deal Island.
Lisa, I saw you down the end
with a big smile.
What's going through your head?
First of all, spoilers
for Deal or No Deal Island.
Like, thanks, guys.
Yeah, I hadn't heard anything
about that.
And I guess it just shows, like,
what sort of game this is, like,
it's so fast that, like, apparently
a whole storyline situation
can be happening that crosses over
the reality TV multiverse.
And I'm just in the dark about it.
It's a Survivor first.
Bucket list. Tick.
So, Cirie,
what's your position on this?
Are you concerned that there's new
information coming out at Tribal?
Um, I'd be foolish not to say
it raises an eyebrow.
Um...
..but whether she played
Deal or No Deal with David or not,
um, doesn't affect the relationships
that I'm building here.
So, Parvati, what's tonight's vote
about for you?
Well, for me,
I'm voting out the person
who's trying to blindside
or not even.
It's not a blindside anymore.
It's very clear
that he wants to vote me out.
So, I just think that what Rob
has done
to try to throw a huge target on me
is helping him
try to get the target off of him.
I don't really get down with someone
who wants to have control over
everybody else.
So I think I've made it clear
where my vote is going.
Alright, well,
I think it might be time to vote.
Yeah. Because I've got a question.
Alright. It is time to vote.
Cirie, you're up.
Lucky me.
Why did I have to go first?
Well, here goes nothing.
This is just a backup
in case an idol gets played.
You tried
to blindside me on my birthday.
I'm not mad.
I'm just disappointed.
I'll go count the votes.
If anyone has an idol
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
Alright, I'll read the votes.
First vote. Cirie.
Rob.
That's one vote Cirie. One vote Rob.
That's two votes Rob.
One vote Cirie.
Rob.
Three votes Rob.
One vote Cirie.
First person voted out
of Australia versus the World.
Rob.
That's four votes. That's enough.
You need to bring me your torch.
Good job.
Rob, the tribe has spoken.
That's it. Time for you to go.
Cheers, mate. Good luck, guys.
Bye, Rob.
Bye.
Well, this tribe might want
to be the United Nations,
but one thing is clear,
World peace is a long way off.
Before you go,
I've got something for you.
You might need this.
There you go, Lisa.
Alright. Grab your torches.
Head back to camp. Good night.
Australia's most notorious players...
GEORGE: Golden God
up against the best-ever winner.
..take on global megastars...
If you come for me
and I didn't send for you,
you're going
to get your torch snuffed.
..in a supercharged season...
This is like playing
in a grand final every single day.
..where the highest honour
is up for grabs.
I'm here for the glory.
I want the world title.
But only one...
I'm coming in here guns blazing,
ready to win.
..can be the world's first...
Everybody will bend their knee
to their king.
..international...
Come on, let's go, Aussie.
..sole survivor.
Let's get this party started.
World tribe
decided to blindside me.
I can kind of understand why.
Um, massive threat in the game.
I was the only thing standing
between them and the Australians.
And now they
will be sliced apart.
Rob. I'm so sorry, man, but you
interfered with the mission
the Americans were sent here
to accomplish.
I truly thought
they had brains in them
to realise that the only way to
beat the Australians
is to work together as a team.
I can 100% guarantee an Aussie
will win sole survivor now.
Without a shadow of doubt.
Captions by Red Bee Media